freedom251info.com 2018-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Tech News in Trend

We at **Freedom 251 Info** have a comprehensive privacy policy. The only motive of this policy is to safeguard the anonymity of the information given by all those who are/were somehow related with our company. We have devised an unambiguous and strict guideline pertaining to the obtainment, use, and furnishing of personal information, like name, e-mail id, mobile number, etc. that we receive from our esteemed users. The personal information that you provide, remains completely confidential with us and we do not in any case unless directed by the court of law, disclose your personal information to anyone. The information that we get from you, rest assured that it will never be exposed to any nefarious practices.

####  **The Information that we Need**

 _We need only those information that is needed to identify the personal information of a person, viz. first and last name, the gender, address, e-mail id and mobile number and the business type, a particular person is interested in. This information is needed as they are required in order to provide a particular service or completing a transaction._

####  **Giving Personal Information**

Freedom 251 Info neither shares nor transfers any of your Personal Information, except the conditions mentioned below:

  * We do not disclose the personal information of our esteemed users unless we are directed to do so by the honorable court. However, we may make some of your information known under the following situations:
  * We may, if the situation of the circumstances necessitates it, share your personal information with our partners, so that they could be able to better fulfill your personal needs and requirements.
  * We may, if the need arises, share some of your personal information to a third party, but that sharing will be used for the purpose of providing you a better service and not otherwise.

####  **The purpose for which we use your information**

The information that we collect from you is used for honest purposes only, and not otherwise. The information that we collect from you is used:

  *  **To know your personalized needs and requirements:** The information about you, help us know about your individual preferences and these, in turn, help us better our services and personalize your experience.
  *  **To improve the work experiences of our website:** We try our level best to improve the offerings of our website and give our users better experiences, based on the information and feedback that we receive from you.
  *  **To better our customer service:** The specific information that we receive from our customers like you, help us better our customer services and cater to their support needs.
  *  **To send emails periodically:** We use your email addresses to send you the email that is relevant, based on your specific preferences, needs, and requirements.

####  **Links to other Website**

The privacy policy tends to vary from one website to the other. We are not liable, even remotely, for any type of wrongful disclosure that may arise owing to the privacy policies of other websites linked to us. Therefore, it is your sole responsibility to go through the privacy policies adopted by any other website that you visit.

####  **Contact Information**

Email: **freedom251info@gmail.com**

Privacy Policy

Is this Post Helpful?
